previously on "Desperate Housewives"
前情回顾
why don't I just marry you?
我可以娶你呀！
I've gota fantastic health plan.
我的医疗保险很好
You'd be covered instantly.
你就用我的好了
susan got an offer she couldn't afford to refuse.
Susan遇到了一个无法抗拒的机会
You've had too much to drink.Give me your keys.
你喝的太多了 把你钥匙给我
Bree rejected a helping hand.
Bree拒绝了别人的帮助
I want to have a babywith you.
我想为你生个孩子
Gaby gave carlos the answer he'd been waiting for.
Gaby终于给carlos一个梦寐以求的答案
You're my second a-b negativetoday.
你是今天献血志愿者中第二个AB血型
-Oh,who is it?
-还有谁？
That guy.
那个人
And zach began to put "a" and "b" together.
zach似乎发现了一些端倪
Susan mayer had always believed
Susan mayer一直认为
the punishment should fit the crime.
罪有应得的观点是正确的
She first came to this conclusion
她当初下这个结论
when she discovered her husband karl had been unfaithful.
是在她发现丈夫karl对她不忠的时候
Since karl had destroyed the love she had given him...
既然karl如此不珍惜她的爱...
Susan felt it was appropriate
Susan觉得她也可以报复
she destroy the things he loved in return...
弄坏karl心爱的东西...
one by one.
一个接一个
but now,three years after their divorce,
但是如今 就在他们离婚三年之后
susan was reunited with karl once again...
susan又要同karl复婚了...
susan,
As partners in a crime of their own.
这次他们一起要玩点花样
This is insurance fraud. We could both go to jail.
这次就是诈骗保险 弄不好 我们都得坐牢
Now we can't tell anyone we're getting married.
所以我们绝对不能对外人说起这事
I know.I was listening to you.
我知道 我听着呢
Now the prenup'sall set.
婚前协议准备好了
You can sign itat the courthouse.
你到时候在法庭上签一下
11:30,wednesday morning.Right?
周三11点半 是吧？
Right. And your surgery'sstill on for thursday?
对 你手术是在周四？  是的
Good. The insurance kicks inthe minute we say "I do."
很好 只要我们说“我愿意” 保险就生效啦
I know no one's asking me,but
我想插句话
I think this whole thing is a tragic mistake,
我觉得你们这么做 实在是犯了一个很严重的错误
and I just don't have it in meto survive another ugly divorce.
而且我可没法承受你们再次离婚的打击
Don't worry,honey.This time, it is strictly a business arrangement.
别担心 亲爱的 这次完全是交易  最好是
'cause if I see so muchas one lingering gaze between the two of you,
如果我要是看到你们俩眉来眼去的
I swear I'll go to the insurance companyand turn you in.
我发誓要去保险公司告发你们
So we shouldn't expecta wedding gift,huh?
看来我们的结婚礼物泡汤了
Oh,can you grab meyour wedding ring?
你能把结婚戒指拿过来吗？
I wanna get it cleanedbefore the ceremony.
我想在结婚前擦干净点
I mean,do we have to dothe whole ring thing?
我们非得要戴上戒指吗？
Of course we do.It's gotta look believable.
当然要 这样别人才信以为真
Yeah,okay.Well,I'll just
好吧 我就
grab somethingout of my jewelry box.
随便从珠宝盒里拿点东西吧
Susan,that ringwas my grandmother'S.
Susan 那戒指可是我祖母留下来的
One day it's gonna be julie'S.
julie结婚时也要戴呀  戒指在哪里？
I don't know...
我不知道...
That was a family heirloom. I trusted you with it.
那可是祖传下来的啊 亏我还这么信你 把戒指给你
Well,I trusted you not tocheat on me and break my heart.
当初我认为你不会发生婚外恋 让我伤心呢
Oh,my god. Oh,my god.
哦 天啊 天啊
What--what did you do with it?
戒指到底怎么了？
I threw it out my car windowsomewhere on route 7.
我在第7大道时 扔到车窗外去了
What?! When?
什么？！什么时候？
The nightyou abandoned me.
就在抛弃我的那晚  Suz--
karl,you are so not allowed to get angry.
karl 你凭什么对我发火？
I mean,I might've been the oneto throw away the wedding ring,
我只不过扔了结婚戒指
but you threw awaythe whole marriage.
而你却丢弃了这个婚姻
There was plenty of bad behaviorthat went on back then,
当时大家脾气都不好
so just get offyour high horse.
所以你也别自命清高了
We're on the same page now, so we shouldjust focus on that.
现在我们是一条船上的人了 我们得办正事
yes,susan mayer believed the punishment should fit the crime.
没错 susan mayer关于罪有应得的观点一点没错
Karl,I thinkthere might be snakes in here.
Karl 这里好像有蛇
We're not leaving hereuntil you find that ring.
找不到戒指 我们就不走
so did karl.
karl自己不也是嘛
Desoerate Housewives Season 02 Episode 15
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 少数派 CamuS Bryan 校对: 少数派 时间轴: gagagao
Sync: YTET-gagegao -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第十五集
it was a tradition at leonardo's bar and grill,
leonardo烧烤酒吧有这么一个传统
an hour before closing time,
打烊前的一个小时
a waiter would sing a selection of ridiculously depressing italian arias.
一位服务员要唱一系列的悲情的意大利咏叹调
It was also a tradition that the only customers who would actually listen
而真正在听的却是
were the ones already depressed to begin with.
那些本来就哀伤的顾客
tony?
Do you have to rush off?
别急着走
I thought maybe we could just chat for a minute.
我想和你聊聊
So I haven't seen you in a while.
好久不见你了
Well,I didn't wanna come here because I was afraid
我之所以没来是因为我担心
it would drudge up memories of my husband.
这里会让我想起我的丈夫
You know, this was our place.
你也知道 这是我们俩常来的地方
Rex passed away recently.
Rex最近去世了
He was,um,murdered
他是被
by our pharmacist.
我们的药剂师杀死的
I hope you changed pharmacists.
希望你换了药剂师
I didn't have to. He committed suicide.
那倒不必了 他畏罪自杀了
Look,you've had a little too much wine tonight.
您今晚喝了不少酒了
How about I call you a cab?
要不要我给您叫出租车？
Oh,no,no,no,no. I'm okay.
不 不 不 我没事
Your car would be safe in our lot,
您的车可以停放在我们停车场里
and you can pick it up tomorrow.
你明天再来取也不迟啊
Please.
行吗？
Well,okay.
好吧
Tony?
How many more arias is he gonna sing?
还要唱几首咏叹调？
Five.
5首
Oh. In that case,
哦 既然这样
why don't you bring me another bottle of the pinot grigio?
你就帮我再拿一瓶灰皮诺干白酒吧
and please hurry.
请务必快点
bree?
Bree.
You okay?
你没事吧？
yes?
什么事？
Hi. Uh,
你好 呃
did you know your mother is asleep on the lawn?
你妈在草坪上睡着了 你知道吗？
Yeah,well,you don't seem terribly shocked.
你看上去怎么一点不震惊？
Oh,it's,um...
哦 其实..
it's just,mom drinks,
其实我妈有酗酒的毛病
and sometimes she sleeps it off in the weirdest places.
有时候就随便找个地方就这么睡着了
Can I help you with her?
我能帮忙吗？
No. No,it's okay.
不用了 没事的
I,uh,I know how to take care of her.
我知道该怎么照顾她
Well,good luck to you then.
祝你好运
I wanna play "chopsticks."
我要弹
-Me too.
-我也要
You okay?
你还好吗？
I'm coming!
来啦！
-hi.
-你好
Hi.
你好
Your kids--they have any allergies I should know about?
你的孩子 他们对什么东西过敏？
Uh,not that I know of. Why?
没有 为什么这么问？
'Cause I'm watching them.
因为我要照看他们呀
Tom called,said you both got pulled into work for the weekend,
Tom打电话来说你们这周末要加班
asked me to baby-sit.
叫我过来照看一下孩子
Really?
真的
I thought it'd be nice if I gave 'em back to you alive.
我想了想 能把孩子照看好等你们回来多好啊
oh,hey,mrs. Mccluskey.
你好 Mccluskey夫人
-Sorry,I forgot to tell you.
-抱歉 我忘了告诉你了
Hi.
你好
Oh,that's okay. Um...
没关系 呃...
would you excuse me just for a second? I have A...
失陪一下 我有点..
thing.
事
-Sure.
-好的
Thanks.
谢谢
Follow me.
跟我来
You're part of the thing.
跟你有关
A million teenagersin this neighborhood, and you hire mccluskey?
这个社区这么多青少年 你偏偏挑了mccluskey?
What's the big deal?
那又怎么了？
Well,for starters,she's ancient!
首先 她老得都成精啦！
shh!This is a thin door!
小声点 这门不隔音！
It was not that long agothat she keeled over in her front yard.
前不久她自己昏倒在自家院子里
A day withour kids will finish the job.
现在再带我们的孩子 她会彻底垮了的
It's only for a few hours.
就几个小时而已
Plus,parker's on a play datewith the farrells,so it's justthe twins and penny.
而且parker去farrell家玩了 就剩下双胞胎和penny
Just the twins and penny?
就剩下双胞胎和penny？
Okay,that was stupid.
哦 这个主意的确不好
Let me try that another way.
我再换种方式说吧
We have to be at workin one hour.
我们得工作1小时
There's no day careon the weekends,
周末托儿所不开
so you cut mccluskey loose,we're stuck.
你要是再不要mccluskey 我们可就没辙了
We will find someone--
我们会找到人的--
someone who doesn't rememberwhat they were doing the day lincoln was shot.
得找一个对林肯总统被暗杀毫无印象的人 （意思是说得找一个岁数小的人）
Fine.
好吧
Let's go break the news.
那我们就告诉她吧
My wife has somethingto tell you.
我妻子有话对你说
So here's the deal.
情况是这样的
Um,there wasa little miscommunication, and as it turns out,
我丈夫误解了我的意思 所以...
we don't need ya.
我们其实不需要你
Okay.
好吧
Fine.I'll just go back home.
那我就回家了
Okay. Sorry.
好的 不好意思
By the way,
对了
your husband was right.
你丈夫说得没错
It's a thin door.
这门是不怎么隔音
Carlos,what are you doing?
Carlos 你在干吗？
Hello,gabriela.
你好 gabriela.
Oh.
哦
Hi,mom.
你好 妈妈
I just told carlosI just had to take a shower.
我刚和carlos说我非要洗个澡不可
The man next to me on the planeweighed 300 pounds,
因为飞机上坐我旁边的那个人重有300磅
and he sweated all over me.
一流汗全跑到我身上了
Ugh,it was so gross.
呃 真恶心啊
No,I'm just surprisedyou're here.
你来这 我真没想到
It's valentine's day.
今天是情人节呀
Don't you and mr. Hedge fundhave plans?
你和你的“对冲基金”先生难道没什么活动吗？
I know carlos and I do.
carlos和我已经安排好了
No,I left charles.
没活动 我和charles分手了
What?
什么？
He was worth,like,$6 million.
他身价可有600万啊
Money is not everything,gabriela.
钱不是万能的 gabriela
For some people, but we're talkingabout you now,mother.
对于有些人来说 的确如此 可我们说的不是别人 是母亲大人你啊
You know,I can't believe this. I mean,I just went througha terrible breakup,
我真不敢相信 我刚刚和男友分手
and the least you could dois pretend to care.
你就不能假装很关心我的样子啊
Well,of course we feel awfulabout it, don't we,gabrielle?
当然 我们都很难过 不是吗 gabrielle?
Yeah,we're justsick about it.
是啊 我们都觉得很讨厌
Well,don't worry about me.
不用为我担心
I'll be okay.
我会没事的
In fact,
其实
I bought myselfa little gift to take my mindoff my problems.
为了让自己开心点 我还特地奖赏了自己
Really?What did you buy?
是嘛？买了什么？
new boobs!
超大胸部！
No peeking,carlos.
可不要偷看哦 carlos
Okay,mom,put these away!
好了 妈妈 快挡起来！
My plastic surgeongave me a great deal.
我的整形师给我做的
Aren't they fun?
是不是很大啊？
bye,carlos.
再见 carlos
What?I think she's charming.
怎么了？我觉得她美丽十足
Okay,you can thinkshe's charming.
行 你可以这么想
But don't forget for one secondthat she is a monster.
但千万别忘了 她是个让人极度生厌的人
did you get the gum outfrom under the diamond?
戒指上的口香糖弄下来了吗？
Mostly.
差不多了
Morning.
早上好
Hi!Happy valentine's day.
好！情人节快乐
Dr. Ron,did you spend the night?
Ron医生，你在这里过夜了？
Well,uh,yeah,I gotkinda tired after the movie, so I asked--
呃，呃，看完电影之后我有点累了 所以我就问-
it's okay. She knowsthat you make house calls.
没关系的，她知道你上门出诊的
Oh. Um,so listen,I've got surgery till 6.
哦，嗯，听着，我6点前有手术
I'll get dressed and I'll pickyou up at about 7.
穿戴好之后7点我来接你
We have reservations at chez naomi.
我们在Chez Naomi订座了
Great! I'll havea light lunch.
太棒了！烛光晚餐
And also,dr. Cunningham'sschedule opened up, so if you'd like,
还有，Cunningham医生有时间了 如果你愿意的话，
we can move upyour surgery to wednesday.
我们可以把你的手术时间提前到星期三
Oh,I have a wedding that day.
那天我要参加一个婚礼
On a wednesday?
在星期三？
yeah.
是的
wednesdays are becomingvery popular with brides.
新娘们喜欢在星期三结婚
It's like the new saturday.
就像周六一样
Okay.
好吧
Well...
那...
I'll see ya tonight.
我们今晚见
Bye.
再见
Your mother isa rotten,sneaky person.
你妈是个狠毒的卑鄙小人
Look,
瞧
I'm not too crazy aboutthis whole fake marriage thing,but
我对假婚事件没什么看法，但...
if you don't havethat operation, you could die.
如果你不动手术的话 可能会死的
So don't be so hardon yourself.
所以对自己别太苛刻了
You are a good person.
你是个好人
Thanks,hon.That really helps.
谢谢，亲爱的 你的话帮我大忙了
Okay,now I want youto go over and slip this ringto your father.
好了，现在过去把这个给你爸爸
And just so you know,if edie catches you,
你知道的，要是被edie抓住了
I'm expecting youto swallow it.
我希望你把它吞下去
How's the hangover?
醒酒好些了吗？
I do not have a hangover,andrew,
我没什么醒酒，andrew
because I was not drunk.
因为我没喝醉
Then,uh...
那 呃...
how abouta little hair of the dog?
要不要再来点酒 借酒醒酒嘛
It'll perk you right up.
那会让你振作起来
Look,for the record,
大家都知道
I had an allergic reactionto my antihistamine medication,
我对抗组织胺剂药物有过敏反应
so I would appreciatejust a little bit of sympathy.
你们总该可怜可怜我吧
Why can't you just drink alonein your room like tammy's mom?
你就不能像tammy妈妈在自己房里喝酒？
For god sakes,it was an honest mistake.
看在上帝份上 我只是一时不小心
I thought I could have just a little bit of winewith dinner,
我以为晚餐时喝点酒没问题
but,apparently,my body couldn't handle it.
可没想到身体承受不了
Fine!
好吧
If it makes everybody happy,
如果能让你们高兴
I will just suffer through my sneezing fitsand my hives on my own.
那就让我发寒 发抖 浑身起疹子好了
there. Is that better?
好了吗？
So basicallyyou would rather drink than to not haveallergies?
所以你宁可满身疹子也不愿意不喝酒？
hi. Is now a bad time?I could really use a favor.
现在有空吗，我需要帮忙
She was beautiful,wasn't she?
She was beautiful,wasn't she? 她很美丽，对吗？
Yeah.
是的
Come on,sit down.Your breakfast is getting cold.
过来，坐这里 早餐快凉了
Was my real motherbeautiful?
我的生母漂亮吗？
Well,she was,uh,
她很漂亮，嗯..
attractive,as I recall.
很有魅力，我记得
Do I look like her?
我和她长的像吗？
I don't know.I-I only met her once.
不知道，我只是见过她一次
Well,'cause ifI don't look like her,then
那...我长的不像她，那
I might look likemy real dad.
我也许和我的亲生父亲很像
I'm getting real tiredof your morbid fascination
我厌倦了你的幻想了
with two strangers who didn'tlove you enough to keep you.
就为了两个根本不爱你 抛弃你的陌路人
So,please,stop asking about them.
别再提他们了
It's only natural that I'd wannatalk about my birth parents.
我讨论我的生父母是很自然的事
Well,
好吧
it may be natural,
或许很自然
but it certainlyisn't polite.
可这是对我的不尊敬
and onceyour daughter was dead,they
你女儿死了
had to get ridof her somehow.
他们就要想尽办法处理掉她的尸体
That's wherethe toy chest came in.
玩具箱就是这么来的
Flash forward 15 years,
15年后
the chest washes upon the shore of rockwater lake.
箱子被冲到了Rockwater湖岸上
Any forensic evidenceis long gone,
所有证据早已经没了
and the youngsget away with murder.
而Young一家人却逍遥法外
Now,of course,the wife,
现在，当然，那个妻子
mary alice,is already dead,but...
Mary Alice已经死了，可是...
paul young'sa different matter.
Paul Young就不同了
If you'd like meto deal with him,
如果你要我对付他的话
just say the word.
尽管开口
Delfino's bringingmy grandson here.
Delfino会把我孙子带来的
I wannaget the kid something.
我要给这孩子一些东西
You know anythingabout those mp3 things?
你听过这些mp3播放器吗?
Yeah,they're real nice.
是的,不错的东西
I'd go with that.
那送就这个吧
Ah,he's probablygot one already.
呃,他可能已经有了
Paul younghas had 16 years to get my grandkidanything he wants.
16年了 Paul Young已经给了 我孙子想要的一切了
Do me a favor,will ya?
帮我个忙,好吗?
Yeah.
好
See to it that
确保
paul young has a toy chestof his very own.
Paul Young手里也有属于自己的玩具箱
-karl!
-Karl?
yeah?
什么事?
This placeis a freakin' pigsty.
这里乱的像猪圈一样
Would you get down hereand help me?
你能不能下来帮帮我?
All right,hold on,it's almost halftime.
没问题,等等,已经快半场了
By the way,I made dinner reservations at chez naomi tonight,if that's okay.
顺便提一下 今晚我在Chez Naomi订了位子
it's gotta be betterthan that rathole you took me toon new year'S.
最好比新年时你带我去的那家鼠窝要好
And don't even think of getting me carnations again.
别以为几束康乃馨就能再打发我
That crap might have flownfor mayer.
那些垃圾丢给Mayer正合适
I actually have taste.
我是有品位的女人
Come on! Move it!
快点给我下来
all right,I'm coming.
好,来了
No! No,no,no.
不 不 不 不
Sit and watch the game. I was just giving youa hard time.
坐那儿看比赛吧 刚刚我过分了一点
You'd had a tough week.
这星期你太忙了
Boys...
Boys... 孩子们...
can you just keep it downjust a little bit?
你们能小点声吗？
Because I have a very...
因为我患了
special typeof grown-up headache.
一种很特别的成人头痛
We need to see mommy and daddy.
我们要见爸爸妈妈
We wanna play 'em our song.
我们要给他们演奏我们的歌
Honey,you can'T.They're at work.
亲爱的，现在不行，他们在上班
Well,can we play itfor you?
那，我们给你演奏好吗？
Sure.
当然可以
just--just a moment,okay?
只是...等会儿，好吗？
All right,boys,let's have it.
好了，孩子们，我们开始吧
When I heard that you twowanted to try for another child,
我听说你们想要第二个孩子
I was delighted.
我实在很高兴
But I had some causefor concern.
但是我也有些担心
Gabrielle,you sufferedsome extensive injuries
Gabrielle，上个月摔下楼之后
during your falllast month,and
伤势比较严重
the test confirmedthere are complications.
测试表明有并发症
You can't have kids?
你不能生孩子了？
Well,the doctor's not100% positive,but
医生还不是完全肯定，但是
it's very,very iffy.
很有问题
Carlos,I am so sorry.
Carlos 我感到很遗憾
I know how muchyou wanted to be a dad.
我知道你很想做爸爸
Thanks.
谢谢了
Don't be so suicidal.We can always adopt.
别当世界末日似的，我们可以领养孩子的
I wanted to have a childof our own. You know that.
我只是要个自己的孩子 你知道的
What does it matterwhose D.N.A. It is?
谁的遗传基因有什么重要？
The diapers are still gonnasmell the same regardless.
尿布味还不是都一样
I'd just prefernot to adopt. Okay?
我就是不喜欢收养 行吗？
Fine.
好
What about surrogacy?
代母生育怎么样？
I mean,I know it's pricey, but at least the babywould look like us,
虽然价格不菲 但是至少孩子会像我们俩
and I wouldn't getstretch marks. It's a win-win.
而且我也不会留下妊娠纹 一举两得
Great.
好极了
So then we havesome stranger off the street giving birth to our child.
那我们就在路上随便拉个不认识的人给我生孩子
Is that what you really want?
这就是你希望的？
What I wantis for you to lighten up.
我希望的就是你能高兴点
We don't havea lot of options, and you're gonna have to pick one.
我们没那么可选的 你只能捡一个
I-I have a thought. Mm?
我-我有个想法 嗯？
Well,it's,uh,a little bit controversial, but,uh,go with me.
这，呃， 有点荒唐 但是，听我说
Well,first of all,let me tell you,
首先，我要告诉你们
that I am in the best shapeof my life.
我现在保养得非常好
-So?
-然后？
So...
这样的话
what if I wasyour surrogate?
我做你们的代母如何？
Yeah,I know. I knowit might sound a little crazy,
是的 我知道 这可能听起来有点疯狂
but I am the only onein the world
可我是独一无二的
that you can trustto put the baby's needs first.
你们可以放心 我会把宝宝放在第一位的
You know,I'll exercise more,I'll eat better--
你知道，我可以多多锻炼 吃的更好
mother,no!
妈妈，不行！
Why?
为什么？
Off the top of my head,you're on medicare?
首先一条 你还在享受国家给65岁以上老人的医疗保障
I am only fifty... one.
我才51岁...
You know,and there's this womanin england last year.
你知道，去年英国有个女人
She was 63 years old,and she gave birth to her own grandchild.
她已经63岁了 可她还生了孙辈们呢
Look,I don't care if she shottriplets out of her ass.
听着，我才不管她是不是能生出三胞胎来
It's not gonna happen.
这不可能发生
Can you believe this?
你能相信这些吗？
How'd thatengland baby turn out?
那些英国宝宝生出来怎么样？
I mean,it didn't have,like, a big head or anything,did it?
我是说，他们没有像大头之类的毛病
Carlos,you are notseriously considering this.
Carlos，你不是真的在考虑这个吧？
Well,think about it,gaby.
考虑考虑，gaby
This way,the surrogate wouldn'tbe some impersonal incubator.
这样的话，代育的就不会是 那些毫无亲情的育婴者了
There'd be a family tie.
是有血缘关系的
I have a migraine.
我头疼
I'm gonna go lay down upstairs.
我上去躺着了
Then when I get up,
我醒来的时候
I hope we can all talk aboutthis like rational human beings.
希望我们能像正常人一样讨论这些
Carlitos,don't worry.
Carlitos，别担心
Just give her time.
给她点时间想想
She'll come around.
她会明白的
boys?
孩子们？
Boys?
Okay,we're done playinghide-and-seek!
好了，捉迷藏游戏该结束了
Boys?!
孩子们？！
Porter! Preston!
This isn't funny!
这不好玩！
Mrs. Mccluskey,hi.
你好，Mccluskey夫人
Have you seenthe scavo boys?
你看见Scavo家的孩子们了吗？
No,can't saythat I have. Why?
没有，我没看见. 怎么了？
I have somethingto tell them.
我有些事要和他们说
Have they signedthe contract?
他们签合同了吗？
'Cause if not,somebody should call bednark and tell them to adjust the language.
如果没有，打电话给Bednark让他们注意措辞
oh. I'm sorry. Hang on.Hello?
哦，不好意思 等会儿 你好？
lynette scavo?
Lynette Scavo吗？
Yes.
是
I believe I have somethingthat belongs to you.
我想我这儿有些你的东西
hi. Excuse me.Hi. You called and you said my kids are here?
你好，打扰了 您打电话说我的孩子在这儿？
hi,mommy!
嗨 妈妈！
-Oh,my god!
-哦，我的天
Dad!
爸爸
Just what were you thinking, taking off like that?
你们究竟在想什么？ 像那样跑了？
honey,I was so worried about you.
亲爱的，我担心死你了
get your stuff.Get your stuff right over here.
拿上你的东西 这里 拿上你的东西
Thank you.
谢谢了
-Thank you so much.
-太感谢了
Stay right here.
就待在这里
I'm just glad I found 'emand not some weirdo freak.
我很高兴我找到他们而不是什么人贩子
Oh,yes.Oh,yeah,me too. Thank you.
哦，是的 是 我也这样觉得 谢谢
Because there are all sortsof crazy people out there--
外面太多形形色色的疯子了
drunks,perverts,molesters.
酒鬼 精神病 还有色狼
Yes! Yeah,no,I know.
是是 不 我知道了
No! You got really lucky.
不！你很幸运
I mean,a different personmight have called the cops or child welfare.
我是说，要是别人应该已经把 他们交给警察或者儿童福利院了
Well,uh,okay,I know how this looks, but I have to tell you,
好，好的，我知道这很不好 但是我得告诉你
I left them witha very reliable baby-sitter.
我把他们托付给了一个非常称职的保姆
Oh,yeah.You picked a real winner.
哦，没错 你选了个非常好的保姆
Are you judging me?Because if you are,
你在指责我？ 如果是的话
-you couldn't say anything
-你根本没资格
lynette,lynette!
lynette，lynette！
-What?!
-什么？
Let it go.
过去就算了吧
The kids walkedfor 3 miles to get here. We don't havea leg to stand on.
孩子们走了3英里路跑到这里 我们腿都快受不了了
Well,thank you so much!
好了，非常感谢
here we go.
我们走
Hey...I don't know about you,
嗨...我不知道你怎么样
but I am tired of allthe tension around here,
可我受够了家里的火药味了
so I was thinking we couldgo shopping, have some fun.
所以我想我们去逛街吧 放松一下
Then maybe later we can talkabout the surrogacy thing,
之后我们再来讨论代生小孩的事
see if we canmake it work.
看看有没有谈得拢的可能性
Oh,gabriela!
哦，gabreila！
Oh,you'll see...
哦，你会发现
this is the best thingfor the entire family.
这是全家人最幸福的事了
So where's the boutique?
那卖衣服的店在哪儿？
Oh,it's inthe hotel lobby.
哦，在旅馆大厅里面
So go ahead,I'm right behind ya.
你先去，我就跟在你后面
Okay.
好的
what are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm going home.
回家
What?
什么？
I thoughtwe were gonna talk about how the surrogacy will work.
我以为我们要谈谈代生小孩的事
Here's how it's gonna work--
这就是结果
you're gonna check yourself into the hotel,
你在旅馆登记
and then tomorrow,you're gonna plant yourchildbearing hips on a plane,
明天，带上你的育儿袋乘飞机
and you're gonnaleave our lives forever.
永远离开我们
I'm pulling out.Watch your boobs.
我要发动了 当心你的胸
come on out.
出来吧
Oh,thank god! I'm so sorry.
哦，谢天谢地 我真的很抱歉
I don't know what happened.I was in the kitchen cleaning upafter making cookies,and
我不知道怎么回事 做完曲奇饼 我在厨房打扫
I looked in the living room,and they were gone.
等我再看客厅，他们就不见了
We tried to tell her we weregoing, but she was asleep.
我们想告诉她我们要走了 可她睡着了
You were sleeping?
你在睡觉？
I most certainly was not.
我当然不是
-Yes,you were.
-就是，你睡着了
Okay,all right,
好吧 好了
that liejust lost you another week of tv and video gameprivileges.
撒谎 你们一个星期不准看电视 玩游戏了
That's two. You wannakeep talking and lose more?
2次了 还要继续撒谎 失去更多玩的机会吗？
Then apologizeto mrs. Van de kamp.
给Van De Camp太太道歉
Sorry.
对不起
All right,go back in.No--no harm done.
好了，快进去 没什么，不是他们的错
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉，实在是抱歉
well,if you ask me,it'sa pretty crappy thing to do.
要是问我的话 我觉得你这么做太不像话了
Did you even slow the car downbefore you pushed her out?
把她推出车之前 你减速了吗？
Okay,first of all,no one asked you.
好了，首先 没人要问你
And the only reason you careabout my mother is because
其次 你关心我妈的唯一原因就是因为
of that ridiculous suggestion she offered.
她那个无比荒谬的提议
I think her offer to be our surrogate was very generous.
我想她能代生是很慷慨的事
Generous?
慷慨？
Don't you seethe strings attached?
你不知道这样做的后果吗？
What strings?
什么后果？
The only reason she offered up her dusty wombis because she's screwed.
她拿出她老旧的子宫为我们生孩子 只是因为她手头紧
Her latest sugar daddygave her the boot,
她新交的蜜糖老爹抛弃了她
so mom needs a place to stayand money.
她要的只是容身之所 还有钱
So trust me,if she carried our child, we'dbe footing the bill for years.
相信我，如果她生了我们的孩子 我们就会跟在她屁股后面付账
I think your hatred for heris clouding your judgment.
我想你对她的偏见影响了你的判断
Maybe,but you don'tknow her like I do.
或许吧，可我比你更了解她
Okay.
好吧
You ran away from home15 years ago.
你15年前离家出走
Did you ever thinkto talk to her about the stuff that happenedbetween you and your stepdad?
想过把你和你继父的事情告诉她吗
It wouldn't have doneany good.
告诉了也不会有用
How do you know that?
你怎么知道
Because...
因为...
she knew exactly what was going on with alejandro,
我和Alejandro的事情她心知肚明
and she chose to look the other way.
可她却置之不理
But you never even gave hera chance to step up. You just ran awayfrom home.
可你从来都没给过她机会 你只知道一走了之
Because if I did,then she w--
因为如果我给了她机会 她就...
because...
因为...
there was a chanceshe wouldn't have believed me,and...
她可能根本不会相信我
and thatwould've hurt a lot worse than anythinghe ever did to me.
那样的痛苦会比Alejandro给我的还要多
She's your mother,and she loves you.
她是你母亲，她爱你
I know it's beena very long time,
我知道事情已经过去了很久
but maybe you cantalk to her about it now.
不过也许现在可以和她谈谈
I'm getting her luggageback to her, and that's the bestI can do.
我把行李拿给她 这是我最大的让步
what are you doing here?
你来干什么
There's something I needto talk to you about. It's important.
有些事要跟你说，很重要
There's nothing for usto talk about.
没什么好说的
Shut up and listen.
闭嘴听我说
Dierdre's father,
Dierdre的父亲，Noah Taylor
noah taylor, somehow found out about zach,
不知何故发现了Zach的事
and he wants to meet him.
他要见他
"Somehow found out"?Like,maybe you told him?
“不知何故”？就是你告诉他的吧
Noah is no friend of mine.
Noah可不是我朋友
But he's very rich and powerful, and he's terminal,
不过他有钱有势，而且快死了
and he wants to meethis grandson before he dies.
他想在死前见外孙一面
Absolutely not.
没门
Well,you'll be surprised,but I agree with you.
也许你会奇怪，但我同意你
Noah destroyseverything he touches,
Noah会毁坏和他有关的一切
is for this guyto get his hooks into zach.
我们俩谁也不想见到 他和Zach有什么关联
What are we supposed to do?
那我们怎么办
You and zach need to vanish. Just stay out of sight
你和Zach得避开一阵子
until naturetakes its course with noah.
直到Noah死了
If we leave,we won't be coming back.
如果我们走了，就不会回来
You'll never seeyour boy again.
你就再也见不到你儿子了
I know.
我知道
Well,happy valentine's day,my darling.
情人节快乐，亲爱的
Isn't thatyour ex-husband?
那不是你前夫吗
Oh,yeah.
哦，对
apparently,they'll let anyone in here.
看来这里谁都能进
Hi.
嗨
Your chocolate souffl閟will be out momentarily.
您的巧克力蛋奶酥马上就来
Oh,we didn'torder souffl?
我们没点蛋奶酥
I orderedas soon as we got here.
咱们刚来的时候我点的
It takes an hour to prepare.
准备起来要1小时
Oh,I really can'T.I'm stuffed.
真的不行，我吃撑了
No,no,no,this you'll wanna try.
不，一定要尝尝
It's their specialty.
是他们的特色菜
I guessI'll have the souffl?
那就来点蛋奶酥吧
Can you excuse mefor a second?
我离开一小会儿好吗
I,um...
我...
I justhave to powder my nose.
我得去补下装
I'm sorry to interrupt.
抱歉打扰一下
Your makeup is all smudged.Come with me. I'll fix it.
你的装都乱了 过来，我帮你补
-What?
-什么
Come on,get up.
快点，起来
Sorry.
抱歉
My makeup is smudged?
我的装乱了?
get in here.
进来
I have some news that'sprobably gonna devastate you.
有条消息可能会让你崩溃
But I wanted to bethe first one to tell you.
不过我想第一个告诉你
Okay.
好吧
Karl is aboutto pop the question.
Karl要说那句话了
You mean,like,marriage?
你是说...求婚？
Oh,I hope I haven't ruinedyour valentine's day.
希望没有破坏你的情人节
-Do you want a tissue?
- 你要面巾纸吗
No,no. I'm okay.
不，没事
I-I'm just... surprised.
我只是...很奇怪
well,congratulations.
恭喜你
what makes you thinkhe's gonna propose?
你怎么会觉得他要求婚的?
Well,I,um,
哦，我...
I was looking throughhis briefcase this afternoon,
我今天下午在翻他的公文包
and I found this ring.
我发现了一枚戒指
And so tonight he keeps pushingthis "special dessert" on me,
今天晚上他又给我准备了特色甜点
so obviously,he's hidden the ring inside.
很明显，他把戒指藏在里面了
A ring!
戒指哦！
what did it look like?
什么样的戒指
Oh,I don't know.
我说不好
18-karat white gold,10 diamonds, engraved accents.
18克拉白金戒 10块钻石，精雕玉琢
I just got a quick peek.
我只偷看了一眼
I think I know that ring.
我想我见过那枚戒指
That's his grandmother's ring. It's a family heirloom.
那是他祖母的戒指 是他们家的传家宝
And,you know, he might just be having itcleaned or something.
他可能只是把它拿去清理或是什么的
Except for one thing-- lying right next to it...
不过还有一点 那戒指旁边...
was a prenup!
还放了婚前协议
Well,karl is a lawyer,and
哦，Karl是做律师的
it could just be a prenupfor another client.
那可能只是其他客户的
Boy,jealousy isone ugly thing up close.
天啊，今天我总算是见识到了 女人嫉妒起来是多么的可怕
Oh,no,edie--
不，Edie...
no,you know what? I'm gonna takethe high road and...
知道吗，我让着你 不和你斤斤计较
If you'll excuse me,I'm
失陪一下，我...
going back to my table
要回到餐桌了
and getting engaged.
还要订婚
oh,hi. Um,
哦，你好
do you see that man over there? Dark hair,handsome.
看到那边那个男的了吗 黑头发，帅帅的
I need you to slip this to himwithout anybody noticing.
趁别人不注意把这个递给他
Be careful!She thinks you're about to propose.
当心！她以为你要求婚了
God,you never stop.
天啊，你就是没完没了
I told you,I'm not divorcing my wife.
我告诉过你我不会离婚了
I'm in this for the sex, and if you can't accept it,then go to hell.
我只为性，如果你接受不了 去死吧
what the hellare you doing?
你在干吗
Well,I thought you saidthis dessert was special.
我记得你说这甜点很特别
When you put itin your mouth and eat it. What is wrong with you?
那是要放进嘴里吃才特别啊 你怎么了啊
Well...
那...
nothing.
没事
Carlos,
Carlos
what a surprise.Come on in.
真想不到  请进
I thoughtyou could use your bags.
我想你需要你的行李
Oh,yes.The perfect timing.
是啊  你来得正好
I just took a shower and neededsomething to change into.
我刚洗了澡，正要找些衣服换
Here,leave it here.This is fine. Thank you.
放这儿吧，谢谢你
Listen,do you have a minute?
听我说，你有时间吗
because I need to talkto you about something.
有件事我得和你谈谈
Hmm,yeah,sure. Sit down.
当然，请坐
Talk as I dress.
你边说，我边换
I'll leave the door openso I can hear.
我把门开着，好听得到你说话
Look,I was,uh,
你看，我...
I was thinkingabout your surrogacy idea.
我在考虑你说的代孕的想法
And I thinkit could be the answer to all of our problems.
我想这样可以解决所有问题 前提是你还同意的话
Yes! I mean,uh,
当然，我是说...
I am.
我同意
but I-I just think that gaby will never let it happen.
不过我想Gaby永远都不会答应
No,no. No,she canbe convinced. I know it.
不，可以说服她，我知道的
Can you please,uh, zip me up?
你能不能...帮我拉一下?
My zipper! It's stuck.
我的拉链，卡住了
you did that so fast.
你动作真快
I know someonewho works out.
看来某人经常这么做哦
As I was saying,
就像我刚才说的
I thinkthe surrogacy idea could work.
我觉得代孕的方法行得通
but you and gaby are gonnahave to mend some fences.
不过你和Gaby可能有些往事要谈
After such a long time,what is the point?
已经这么久了，还谈什么呢
Lucia,please,hear me out.
Lucia，请听我说
There was a lot of stuffthat gaby went through when she was younger--
Gaby小的时候经历了很多
a lot of stuffthat you don't know about.
很多你不知道的事情
And I think that if you wentto her and asked her about it,
我想如果你去问问她的话
then the two of youcould finally get past it.
也许你们俩可以把事情讲清楚
What stuff are youtalking about,carlos?
你在指什么，Carlos?
your second husband,alejandro?
你的第二任丈夫，Alejandro?
When gaby was 15,he assaulted her sexually.
Gaby15岁的时候，被他污辱了
Is that what she told you?
她就是这么告诉你的？
Look,
你看
I know thatit comes as a shock for you to be hearing it from me--
我知道这事由我来说可能比较震惊
carlos,please,I am aware they had sex.
Carlos，拜托，我知道他们有性关系
But it was gabrielawho seduced him.
不过实情是Gabriela勾引了他
Excuse me?
什么?
She was always jealous of me.
她总是嫉妒我
You don't know how many times I caught her wearing my shoes,
你不知道她有多少次偷穿我的皮鞋
trying on my jewelry...
偷戴我的首饰
and I'd scream at her to leavemy things alone,but no,
我喊着让她住手，可就是不行
she wanted whatever I had.
我有什么她都非要不可
Then one night,
一天晚上
she set her sights on alejandro.
她把眼光放到了Alejandro身上
Believe me,
相信我
no one got raped.
没有人被强奸
Lucia,she was only 15 years old.
Lucia，她才15岁啊
You know,a lot of menhave left me over the years,
这些年有很多男人 都莫名其妙地离开我
But when alejandro left, I knew exactly why it happened.
不过Alejandro离开的原因我很清楚
Gabriela made himfall in love with her.
Gabriela让他爱上了她
Oh,it took me so many yearsto forgive her.
我花了好多年才能原谅她
-You forgave her?
-是你原谅她?
But of course.
当然了
I couldn't have offeredto carry her baby unless I had.
不然我也不会要替她怀孩子
karl. Karl!
Karl， Karl
Come here!
过来
Why didn't you answeryour damn cell phone?
为什么不接手机
I turned it off.What's going on?
我关机了，什么事
Where's edie?
Edie在哪儿
She's upstairs.She's been in a pissy mood eversince we left the restaurant.
楼上 我们离开饭店以后她就很生气
I don't know what's wrong with her.
搞不懂她怎么了
She found the ringand the prenup in your briefcase.
她发现了你公文包里的戒指和婚前协议
She thought you were gonna pop the question tonight.
她以为你今晚会向她求婚
-Oh,no.
-不会吧
Oh,yes.
没错
You know,this wholefake marriage thing was okay when nobodywas getting hurt.
假结婚的事情在没人受到伤害的时候倒没什么
What are we doing? It's a lie!
我们在干吗，这是在撒谎
I lost mike over a lie, and now I'm doingthe same thing to dr. Ron,
我为了一个谎言而失去了Mike 可现在跟Ron医生还是老样子
and--and look at edie.She was devastated.
再看看Edie，她伤心透了
I don't think I can go through with this.
我看我没法继续了
You can'tcall off the wedding. How are you gonna pay for your surgery?
婚礼不能取消 你的手术费可怎么办
I don't know. You know,I'll just...I'll sell the car.
不知道，我就...把车卖了吧
Susie,this is your healthwe're talking about.
Susie，这事关你的健康
We're getting married.
我们必须结婚
-Karl--
no.
不
Dr. Ronwould be the first to say that you're doingthe right thing.
Ron医生会第一个支持你
I'll figure out some wayto handle edie.
我会想办法摆平Edie
How? How are yougonna handle edie?
怎么做？怎么才能摆平Edie?
That poor woman's dreamsexploded in her face tonight.
那女人一生的梦想就这样破灭了
You know,it's not likeyou can just go out and buy her flowers,and everything will be better.
不是买几束花就能弥补的
Then I'll propose to her.
那我就向她求婚
Well,that's a little extreme.
那也有点极端了
Not really. I was probablygonna do it eventually anyhow.
也不完全是，反正早晚也要做
Obviously we're gonnahave to get a divorce before I can actuallymarry her.
当然我们得先离婚，我才能娶她
But,uh... what?
不过...怎么了
Nothing. I just...
没事，我只是...
I didn't know thatyou loved her like that.
不知道你对她是那种感觉
She's a great kid.Total package.
她是个好人，一切都好
What's the matter,susie q?Jealous?
怎么了，Susie小可爱？嫉妒了？
no,of course not.
当然不是
Well,okay,this is good because...
好吧，这样挺好，因为...
you know,if this experience
如果这件事
helped you to realize your true feelings,then,uh...
能让你看清你真正的感觉
then we did somethinggood here.
那这就是好事
Yeah. I think we have.
恩，我想是好事
Come here.
来
I can't believeyou thought I was jealous.
想不到你竟然会以为是我嫉妒
It's not like I still havefeelings for you anymore.
我对你又没什么感觉了
You're right.I-I was just fooling around.
没错，我开玩笑的
So? How did it go?
事情怎么样
Fine. I just dropped offthe luggage and left.
还好，我把行李放下就走了
What was that for?
这是为什么
No reason.
不为什么
Hey,I was thinking...
嗨，我在想...
we should look into adoption.
我们应该领养
Seriously?
真的？
But I thought you wanteda kid with your own D.N.A.?
我以为你想让孩子有你自己的DNA
Blood isn't everything.
血缘不能代表一切
Hey!
嘿！
I heard ya lostyour kids yesterday.
听说你昨天把孩子弄丢了
Yeah.
是的
it was cleared up.It was just a little confusion.
没事了，只是一点小误会
Uh,help me out herewith something.
帮我回答个问题
What exactly is ityou look for in a baby-sitter?
你找保姆究竟是为了什么
Excuse me?
你说什么?
Well,I may be ancient,like you say,
也许我是老的成精了，你也这么说
but I've never gotten drunkand lost track of three kids.
可我从来没喝醉酒以后丢了三个孩子
What?
什么?
I smelled wineon bree van de kamp when she was lookingfor your boys.
Bree去找孩子的时候 我闻到了她身上的酒味
That's ridiculous.
-可笑
Is it?
是吗
Yesterday I found her passed outon her front lawn,drunk as a skunk.
昨天我发现她昏倒在自己家的草坪上 烂醉醺醺
I've known breefor years and years.
我认识Bree好多年了
There's no way she was drinkingwhile baby-sitting my kids.
她不可能在带孩子的时候喝酒
So...
所以...
just go spread your poison somewhere else. Okay?
我看你当着我的面说她坏话 找错人了吧？
I just thought I'd do youa favor and let you know,that's all.
我只是想帮你个忙，让你知道真相 就这样而已
Okay,well,thanks.
好吧，谢谢
Hi.
嗨
You,um,you recovered fromall of yesterday's excitement?
你...从昨天的兴奋里恢复过来了吗?
Oh,truthfully,I haven't beenable to get my mind off it.
说实话，我还是忘不掉
What a scare,huh?
太吓人了，是吧
Yeah,
是
althoughI-I still can't figure out how my boysmanaged to sneak past you.
不过我还是想不通 我家孩子怎么会在你的眼皮底下溜走的
Well,you knowhow boys are at the age. They're escape artists.
你知道这个年纪的孩子 他们是逃跑专家
They're like lightning.
就像闪电一样
It's just,penny...
只不过...penny...
-penny?
-Penny?
Well,I mean,
我是说...
wrangle her into the stroller and then
我就是搞不懂Porter和Preston是怎么 把她弄到车上
make it outyour front door withoutyou even noticing.
然后又在你不知不觉的时候跑到前门的
I guessif you'd fallen asleep...
我想如果你睡着了...
it could've happenedlike that,I-I guess.
就有可能会这样，我想
You know,I think,um, I must have been cleaningthe kitchen,and I-
我想可能是我在清理厨房
I justdidn't hear them because of the noisefrom the dishwasher.
可能是洗碗机的声音太吵 所以我才没有听到
Look,I apologize in advancefor how this is going to sound,
我先为下面的话给你道歉
but I have to ask. It's justgonna eat away at me.
不过我要问你，我快忍不住了
Were you drinkingwhile baby-sitting my kids?
你在照看我孩子的时候有喝酒吗
No!
没有
you know,I may have had just the tiniest little bitof chardonnay.
也许我喝了一丁点夏敦埃酒
Oh,gosh,you got drunk,and you passed out.
天啊，你喝醉了，然后昏了过去
Lynette,if I close my eyeseven for a moment,
Lynette，如果我有合上眼睛半秒
it's because of theseantihistamines I've been taking.
那也是因为我一直在吃的抗组胺剂
Really?Is that why you passed outon your front lawn yesterday morning?
真的吗，你昨天早上在草坪上昏倒 也是因为这个？
Now that you're speaking to mein a fairly accusatory tone,
既然你用这种责备的语气说话
may I remind you thatI was doing you a favor?
也许我该提醒你 我是在帮你的忙
You put my kids in danger, and then you lied about it.
你让我的孩子处地危险 而后又为此说了谎
Do you not gethow big that is? Do you have somekind of problem with alcohol?
你知道事情有多严重吗 你有酗酒问题吗
No! The only problem I haveis with your children.
没有，我唯一的问题就是你的孩子
They're incorrigiblebecause you let them run amok.
他们无可救药，都是因为你让他们放肆
And if I hadn'tdrifted off,
就算我没有睡着的话
or stuck on the phoneor upstairs doing laundry.
他们也会等到我上厕所、 接电话，或者洗衣服的时候跑出去
On any given day, how many glasses of winedo you put away?
你一天要喝多少杯酒
I will not be spoken tolike that. I just won'T.
不要用这种态度跟我讲话，不要
now and then,we allneed a little help...
时不时地，我们都需要一些帮助
so we ask for small favors.
于是我们向他人索取一点点关切
Thanks. I owe you one.
谢谢，我欠你一次情
But it's always best to be wary of those eager to come to our rescue.
不过对那些急来的援助 最好带着一颗机警的心
Well,go on.Kiss the bride.
继续，可以吻新娘了
because even the smallest of favors...
因为哪怕是最小的恩惠...
sure thing,tom. I'd be happyto baby-sit for you.
当然，我很乐意做你家保姆
My,have you noticedhow clogged my rain gutters are?
天啊，你看到我家雨水槽堵得多厉害了吗
...Carries a price tag.
...也承载了代价
Yes,everyone has an agenda.
没错，每个人都有自己的打算
I heard about your operation,aunt inez,
听说了你做了手术，Inez姑妈
and I'm jumpingon a plane right now to come and help you out.
我马上飞过去帮你一把
No matter what they may tell us.
无论他们对我们怎么说
No,I'm happy to,
不，我很乐意
and I'm prepared to stayas long as it takes.
我准备在你康复前一直留在你身边
And in those rare instances where there is  no ulterior motive,
然后当在少有的情况下 人们抛开隐含的动机时
we're so taken aback that we may fail to recognize the truth...
我们却惊诧自己没及时发觉...
Do you still think you don't have a problem?
还说你没有问题吗?
that a loving friend has just done us an enormous favor.
一位忠实的朋友又帮了我们的大忙
www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 少数派 CamuS Bryan 校对: 少数派 时间轴: gagagao
Sync: YTET-gagegao -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Desperate Housewives Season 02 Episode 15 -=THE END=-
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第十五集 谢谢观赏